secondlinethemes.com 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy | SecondLineThemes

SecondLineThemes collects and uses information through secondlinethemes.com or through other ways of online communications (such as newsletter list or social networks) for the purposes defined within this privacy policy.

Information collected includes any personal information provided in contact requests, online purchases, or when subscribing to our newsletter list. We do not collect any personal information that you do not expressly provide.

 **We do not and will never sell, rent, share, or publish your personal information to any third party.**

We do collect anonymous info such as IP addresses, country/location, device used etc. in order to analyze our site traffic. This standard information is collected and stored via Google Analytics. This info is never linked to a specific user, as the info is anonymous.

We may use cookies (tiny files that can be stored locally on your computer, so you can save some info related to your current session, for example). You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings within your browser.

When you make a purchase on our website, you have to insert payment information and some basic personal details. We do not, and will never see, receive, store, or share your financial details. These are all handled by our chosen Payment Gateway providers (2Checkout Inc. and FastSpring Limited).

In the case you want us to fully delete the transaction log and/or details of your purchase, feel free to contact us via email.
